import { QuestionType } from "@/components/question/multipleChoice";

export const fractionRatioQuestion1Data: QuestionType = {
  question:
    "Which of the following represents the same quantity as the ratio 3:4?",
  options: ["3/4", "4/3", "6/8", "2/3"],
  answer: "3/4",
};

export const fractionRatioQuestion2Data: QuestionType = {
  question:
    "If the ratio of apples to oranges is 5:3, what fraction represents the proportion of apples to the total number of fruits?",
  options: ["5/8", "3/5", "3/8", "5/3"],
  answer: "5/8",
};

export const fractionRatioQuestion3Data: QuestionType = {
  question: "What is the ratio equivalent to the fraction 7/10?",
  options: ["7:10", "10:7", "14:10", "10:14"],
  answer: "7:10",
};

export const wordProblemQuestion1Data: QuestionType = {
  question:
    "A recipe requires a ratio of 2 cups of sugar to 5 cups of flour. If you want to use 10 cups of flour, how many cups of sugar are needed?",
  options: ["4 cups", "5 cups", "6 cups", "12 cups"],
  answer: "12 cups",
};

export const wordProblemQuestion2Data: QuestionType = {
  question:
    "The ratio of cats to dogs in a pet store is 3:2. If there are 30 cats, how many dogs are there?",
  options: ["20", "15", "25", "18"],
  answer: "20",
};

export const wordProblemQuestion3Data: QuestionType = {
  question:
    "A group of students is divided into two groups in the ratio 4:5. If there are 36 students in total, how many students are in each group?",
  options: [
    "16 in the first group and 20 in the second group",
    "20 in the first group and 16 in the second group",
    "18 in each group",
    "12 in the first group and 24 in the second group",
  ],
  answer: "16 in the first group and 20 in the second group",
};

export const replacementQuestion1Data: QuestionType = {
  question:
    "A school bus can either sit 24 adults or 36 children. If it already has 12 adults on the bus, how many more children can it sit?",
  options: ["12", "18", "24", "30"],
  answer: "18",
};

export const replacementQuestion2Data: QuestionType = {
  question:
    "A tank can be filled by pipe A in 5 hours and by pipe B in 8 hours. If both pipes are open together, how long will it take to fill the tank?",
  options: ["3.2 hours", "4 hours", "4.6 hours", "6 hours"],
  answer: "3.2 hours",
};

export const replacementQuestion3Data: QuestionType = {
  question:
    "A factory produces 60 widgets per hour. If 3 machines are working, how many widgets will be produced in 4 hours?",
  options: ["180 widgets", "240 widgets", "300 widgets", "720 widgets"],
  answer: "720 widgets",
};

export const replacementQuestion4Data: QuestionType = {
  question:
    "A boat can travel 120 miles in 4 hours. How far can it travel in 7 hours at the same speed?",
  options: ["140 miles", "210 miles", "240 miles", "300 miles"],
  answer: "210 miles",
};

export const replacementQuestion5Data: QuestionType = {
  question:
    "A mixer can blend 40 liters of juice in 15 minutes. How many liters of juice can it blend in 1 hour?",
  options: ["80 liters", "120 liters", "160 liters", "200 liters"],
  answer: "160 liters",
};

export const replacementQuestion6Data: QuestionType = {
  question:
    "If a car can travel 150 kilometers on 10 liters of fuel, how many liters of fuel are needed to travel 375 kilometers?",
  options: ["15 liters", "20 liters", "25 liters", "30 liters"],
  answer: "25 liters",
};

export const replacementQuestion7Data: QuestionType = {
  question:
    "A box can hold 18 liters of liquid. If a shipment contains 144 liters of liquid, how many boxes are needed to hold all the liquid?",
  options: ["6 boxes", "7 boxes", "8 boxes", "9 boxes"],
  answer: "8 boxes",
};
